What a blessed day!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah.
We had to stop the testimony but I will only listen to just one
that will usher us to the next blessing.
I saw many prophetic words - that was last Sunday.
A lot.
That is the way God moves.
And when you are called or you are touched or you have a message from God,
here is message, here is solution.
What is not done well is not done at all, and God is always complete.
Hallelujah, thank you. Let's listen.
Prophecy Time
There is a young lady there, at the back of the sister wearing spectacles.
At the back there.
A very young lady.
It has been a problem for you. You have been bedwetting.
Come, don't be shy.
Prophecy Time
I said you have been bedwetting.
Yes, sir.
What a beautiful girl.
This thing has been disgracing you, even when you were in school.
Yes, sir.
Yet, the thing refuses to leave you.
Come out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Come on! Leave her!
Out!
Who are you?
I want to destroy her!
How?
She will never get married.
What have you done to her?
She has a bright destiny.
What else have you done to her?
What have you pushed her to do?
She is my daughter.
Thank You, Jesus!
I cause her to bedwet.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am the ancestral spirit.
How did you enter her?
Through dreams.
Man of God, the prophecy you gave to my daughter is one hundred percent correct.
She has been bedwetting since childhood up to this age, while in university.
This has made her not to relax in school; she's always on and off.
Each time this thing happened, I would cry.
I wouldn't know what to do.
I thank God today that her case has been opened.
- Thank You, Jesus!
- Thank you.
Man of God, what you said about me is true.
I have been bedwetting since childbirth.
It has been disgracing me wherever I go.
It doesn't allow me to go out.
Wherever I go, it disgraces me.
You said what?
I can't go out.
Sometimes I think I have to be awake so I won't disgrace myself or litter the bed.
How do you cope in the university when you are bedwetting all the time?
Sometimes, my roommates will be -
I am on the top bunk, when I urinate, it will touch the person below me.
So, the urine touches them?
Yes, sometimes, I have to sleep on the floor so I will not disgrace myself.
I will wake up very early to clean the floor and wash my clothes.
She said she sleeps on the floor and wakes up early to clean the urine.
So, don't worry, it's over!
Prophecy Time
The coming Sunday, you will come out to tell the world what happened to you.
OK, it's alright.
Glory be to God.
Hallelujah.
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Today is the coming Sunday we talked about.
The whole thing happened last Sunday.
You can see the move of God.
The whole thing comes directly by vision.
Like she was called, she came out and immediately,
without touching her, stretching hand, you can see that demon cried out.
Behind every situation you are in, lies demon.
Demon is responsible.
Demon is the cause.
Let's hear from her.
After the prayer last Sunday, what happened?
Yes, hear from her.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Sochima Ukpaka.
I am a student of Godfrey Okoye University, a private institution.
I am in 300 level and I am studying psychology.
The prophecy the man of God gave to me last week was true.
I was sitting right there.
Then he said, there is a young lady here, you have the problem of bedwetting.
You are seated at the back of the woman wearing spectacles.
First of all, my mind was not there.
Something tapped me, "This woman in front of you is wearing spectacles".
I said, "Jesus, it is me!" - I ran out.
This issue of bedwetting has been disturbing me.
It has caused me so much pain for the past twenty years.
Since my secondary school days I have known that "Yes, this is bedwetting".
This situation caused me not to stay in a boarding school during my secondary school
though I wanted a boarding school but my mom, as the kid I was,
she said, "'No, you will not go to a boarding school".
I asked her, "Why?"; she said, "That is known to me; don't worry".
With time, I grew up. When I was in SS 1, it was then that I understood what bedwetting was.
During that time, the issue of bedwetting disgraced me severely.
It did not disgrace me as much as when I entered the university
because I was under my mom's care, and she would try to cover me up, no matter what it was.
The shame was not there as compared to at the university level.
When I was seeking for admission, my mom was looking for a university near to us,
just because of this issue of bedwetting.
Then came a time that it stopped; I was not experiencing it.
So she said, "Okay, you can live in the boarding, in the university".
When I went back to school, in my first year, this situation disgraced me on several occasions.
In a room, there were four students.
In the boarding school - some people who know how we live in a boarding school -
there is a place where two or three stay in a room but this one we were four.
That day because I came in newly, I was in the up bunk.
When I was in the up bunk, I was sleeping.
I just slept off.
Then I bedwetted.
It touched the person who was down.
Then, another case was on broad daylight like this.
I just came back from school, and I was sitting down on the bed of another person.
I just dozed off; within five minutes, I had bedwetted on someone else's bed.
When I woke up, I started crying, "What will I do now?
If this person comes back and sees this, what will she tell me?"
In order to be clever, I took the bed up to my own side,
took my own bed to her's and washed her bed sheet.
Then, after I washed it, when she came back, she said, "Why did you wash my bed sheet? Did I beg you?"
I told her, "No, I was drinking Fanta and mistakenly it poured.
So I didn't want her trouble, that is why I washed it".
I thought that was okay.
But often, it started occurring to the extent that they knew about it.
Whenever all these things happened, I would run to my mom.
She would tell me, "Continue praying, God will hear your prayers".
I would say, "Praying? Since you have been praying for me, nothing has happened".
She was telling me, "Continue praying, have that faith".
It disgraced me in my cousin's place in the village.
It disgraced me in many places in this life. I couldn't go out.
In order not to be cleaning up, because it is not every day one would be washing one's bed sheets -
because people around would say, "This girl is so clean; she is washing her bed sheets every day".
They would feel like you are so clean, but they would not know the situation you are passing through.
But even if you wash the bed sheets, the bed itself - even if you take it outside for the sun to touch it,
the smell sometimes would come out, and what would you tell them?
So it resulted in me sleeping on the floor.
I started sleeping on the floor and I would wake up as early as anything,
just to wash and clean up.
Sometimes for people not to be suspicious of what was happening,
I would put it into a plastic bag and take it back home
for my mom to wash, to help me and wash it so that I would not be disgraced.
Could you share with us your experiences and what happened till now?
Daddy, after the prayer, I went back to the hotel room.
I was like, "Are you serious? Just like that? I'm not sure it is true".
Then I went home. My mom said, "Have faith, it is done", and I said, "Okay, let's see".
I took six sachets of water that night.
Normally, I wouldn't take water or anything from 5 or 6 pm.
So I took water and drank all and made sure that I was full enough.
I said to myself, "Okay, let's try it".
I went to bed; I just laid down.
Normally, even if I wanted to pray or do something,
sometimes I would sleep off, or something would happen.
So that day, I brought out my faith bracelet and said, "How will I start now?"
I brought out my faith bracelet and said, "Okay, they are doing like this" - I started meditating
I was counting, and I asked myself, "What will I say?"
I remembered that they said, "Oh Holy Spirit, take more of me and give me more of You".
I was like, "Okay, let's start with that one now".
I started counting it.
As I was doing that, I just slept off and woke up around 9.
Normally, I had to wake up like four or five times.
During those processes of waking up, I would be tired of sleeping and say, "Let me not sleep,
let me just be awake so that if the urine comes, I will just go and urinate".
But this time I did not wake up; I just slept and woke up without bedwetting on the bed.
And since then, for the past seven days, I have never bedwetted, I have been sleeping.
And before now, it happened every day?
Before now, I bedwetted every day.
I got used to it. I was like, "When I wake up, I'll just wash".
It was a normal thing; that was it.
But when I woke up that morning, I was like, "Hey, let me go and wash it. It is morning now".
So I woke up, looked around, "I'm dry!
Okay, let me check the floor, maybe I was turning and urinated on the floor".
I checked the floor, smelled my clothes and was like, "Ah, this is true!"
So I am free indeed.
Did you listen to that?
Being a young girl, she has never experienced this kind of thing.
They have gone to many places.
Okay, let's see. Where will I start?
This is to tell you that when it is your time, or when you meet a man God sent to you,
whether you believe or not, it will definitely happen
but that your belief will only help you to maintain that God send the man to give you.
When the prophecy concerning her was given, she looked back and said, "Are they calling me?"
She was not here because of that situation, she just believed that it was a normal way life
and it would continue like that - it was a different thing she was here for.
But even after the deliverance, she began to ask herself,
"Does it mean I'm free? Is that how things happen?"
When you meet a man that God sent to set you free or deliver you,
it may not be a man, it may be an object.
You know God can use anything, not necessarily a human being.
An object - it could be water or anything.
Whether you believe it or not.
You may not believe but it will happen but to now maintain that blessing, your belief is important.
This is what youths need now to come back to God.
Youths - their hearts are so hardened.
The young people today - this is what they need to come back to God.
When you tell them about Jesus and you are very eloquent,
they will tell you they have studied it in the university.
But they want to see what they have not and what they cannot study in university happens to them.
What happened now?
Call youths and begin to preach about Jesus, about God.
They will tell you, "Look, we have studied all this in school".
Those who have not studied this in school, they will say, "No, I can take a book and read about it".
They want to experience what they have not studied in university and what they cannot study in the college.
They are yearning for a new thing, a new wave, a new direction, a new course.
This is why it is difficult for us to change or tame our youths or mentor our children.
These days, you cannot mentor your children. You go this way, they go that way
because all you are telling them, they know better than you.
Man of God, I want to thank you for allowing God to use you to deliver me
because I felt like all hope was lost; I felt isolated.
I didn't want to come close to people.
I would be like, "If you knew the problem I am passing through,
would you like to be my friend and the rest?"
I felt that this was my world, that that was how I had to face it.
Can we ask you one question and I want you to be free and tell us.
While you were going through this problem,
what were you actually thinking up to do with your life?
They are problems that your parents cannot help you, nobody can help you with.
In this situation, you have many things you keep to yourself
which you did not want to tell anybody and you were always thinking about.
What were you thinking to do with your life while going through this problem? Tell us.
So many times I felt like committing suicide.
I felt like, "Let me end it all.
How can I come out in front of people and tell them I'm bedwetting?"
Even when suitors came, I would be like, "Are you people serious?
If you knew what I am, that I am bedwetting,
would you want a bedwetter as your wife or anything?"
I just felt like committing suicide so many times.
I've tried to do it in front of my mom, and she would tell me, "Stop it; it is not the end of the world".
It's over. That's why we are asking you questions; we are not making jest.
We are happy with you, and we want to learn.
Did you ever think that one day, you will meet a man in your future
that will accept you with that bedwetting?
As beautiful as you are, a man will accept to marry you with that bedwetting? Tell us.
No.!
Why?
I concluded that I would not get married; I didn't want to get married.
Because I feel like it is a shame - who will accept me, no matter what it is?
Will you rise up and give glory to God.
Give glory to God.
When she was sharing the testimony, you'll just look at it, she's a bedwetter, God has healed her.
You never knew that it is more than that.
Inside her, she was planning to commit suicide.
She said...
And all this, she kept away from her mom.
With that, she could never be an obedient child to her mom
because she felt there was something a parent cannot solve.
"This problem - my parent cannot solve it." - this is where disobedience comes.
"Ah, I have this problem, who can solve it? Nobody!"
Definitely the thought of not obeying your parents.
Give thanks to God for this.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
There were many things she was keeping them away from you.
She is right.
Because she thought since you could not help her...
Okay, what else again?
You saw her then as an obedient child, she tried to be obedient
but she had a thorn in her flesh which no one could...
If it is cancer - no problem. Nobody will know, until it is very serious.
But this one, you can't keep it. For how long will you keep it?
All the students knew about it.
If you keep it away from the man you want to marry, after you get to the house of the man,
one week or two weeks, the man will know.
So let's hear from you: What message do you have for the viewers all over the world?
I advise the viewers all over the world to have faith.
You are now preaching faith?
Glory be to God. She said you should have faith.
A faithless generation now has faith.
She said, have faith.
I preached to them to have faith because as I was made to understand, joy is the fruit of faith.
So have faith; God is the God of the last hour - no matter the time or when you feel, all hope is lost.
Just believe in God, always trust in Him; He will do it.
He is the One who makes the impossible to be possible.
So just have faith in Him.
And to the youth out there:
There are so many situations which you are passing through.
You feel it is the end of the world.
It is not the end of the world; run to God.
He is the only true Father that never fails.
Thank you, clap for her.
Mama, are you happy?
Yes, I am very happy.
Now, you are having a child.
Before, she belonged to someone, not you.
She was a child you could lose then in the past suddenly.
But now, here you have a child.
Let me ask you a question: When you knew that your daughter was going through all this situation,
what was your effort to rescue her?
What effort?
Tell us, just in a nut shell.
At what time did you know about it?
And at the same time, did she actually try to keep this challenge away from you
or was she open to let you know any time this situation happened?
Was she open to you? Tell us.
My name is Mrs Ukpaka.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I discovered this when she entered secondary school, because at that time,
she was supposed to be free, not to be bedwetting, so when I now noticed that
I went closer to her and asked her some questions.
She started telling me that, in fact, she didn't like what she was seeing.
That it was better for her to die.
So I told her that it was not the best to...
She said it is better for her to do what?
To die.
Okay, she has told you this.
That was what made me to even go closer to her.
So I never allowed her to stay alone.
So you knew that she was nursing to die.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
When I noticed it, I took her to the hospital for the first time to check her system.
They said that nothing was wrong with her.
I went to many places for prayers and there was no solution.
I now said that I must come here with her
because I know that this is the only place where I will have a solution to that problem
and that was why I brought her.
God is good all the time!
Thank you. Hallelujah.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
While you are sitting down, wherever you are, viewers all over the world,
begin to compare your situation to this lady's situation.
What kind of situation are you having that can be compared with her former situation?
This is how faith comes.
Many of you think you have to read the Bible from Genesis to Revelation.
Faith is natural.
Immediately you realise that God is reliable, with what you are seeing now, He is reliable.
This shows Jesus is reliable.
Jesus is what?
He is reliable.
Immediately you agree and believe Jesus is reliable, faith grows spontaneously, naturally.
It comes just like that and you begin to build on that.
So you need to now establish it - "Ah, Jesus is reliable, I can rely on Him. He will never fail".
No matter the situation you have, you are looking for faith.
"How will I get faith. I will memorise the Bible.
I will read my Bible from Genesis, go to church every day."
Yes, good.
It is a good idea.
But one of the shortest ways to have that faith in God is the one we have just witnessed now.
You have heard, you have seen
and the lady is confessing what she went through
and you saw how she was spotted and she came out.
And immediately, "By the name Jesus Christ, be delivered!", she screamed, "Hii!"
Without touching her - immediately.
Now, it is over!
When you now sit down and meditate over and over and turn it over and over in your heart...
Tell your neighbour, "Turn it over and over in your heart".
Turn it over and over in your heart.
I can't hear you.
I say, what you hear now, what you have seen now, turn it over and over again in your heart.
Tell your neighbour.
Turn it over and over in your heart.
I can't hear you.
Again and again.
Turn it over and over in your heart.
Yes, you have to.
Now you have seen what happened, it is time now to turn it over and over again in your hearts.
Here faith comes.
Only faith pleases God.
Begin to turn it over and over.
Tell your neighbour, "Begin to turn it over and over in your heart".
Begin to turn it over and over in your heart.
In your heart - that is, in a natural way.
We call it thinking but it is not thinking - meditation
because when you think, thinking is here - meditation is above thinking.
Faith prevails over thinking processing.
If you now use the word 'thinking', you are not right.
Begin to meditate over and over again in your heart.
How do we think?
The word 'thinking' naturally is "I am poor. Will my prayers be answered today?
Will this man discover me in the midst of people?
Will this man fetch me out just in the same way he fetched this lady?
What time are we leaving here today?
I don't know.
I still feel the pain.
Will the man pray for me?
But I'm feeling hungry now. If I leave here, somebody will take over my seat.
I will not leave and I'm pressed now. I will endure".
These are the thinking.
Thinking means, what we don't mean.
Often, you don't mean it. By the time I meet you, you change because it is not from your heart.
Oftentimes, what we think, we don't mean it.
Tell your neighbour, "Oftentimes, what we think, we don't mean it".
But if you are able to meditate over an issue, you mean it because it is from your heart.
What is going on in your heart now is thinking.
Tell your neighbour, "What is going on in your heart now is thinking".
Your mind is floating; it is floating.
By the time I want to pray for you, you say, "Is he going to fall me?"
You will not say it out, but in your mind.
Immediately I face you, because you normally see the way people are rolling on the floor
and fall down, and you know they will be looking at you at home...
You say, some people just believe that once you fall, you are a witch or wizard
whereas there is nothing like that.
People just believe once you fall, "Ah!".
But you know when you fall down, people will say "Ah, we saw when they were delivering you.
We didn't know that you are the cause of our problems".
Many people are here today, immediately I get to them, this is the way you see them standing.
In their heart they say, "Is he going to fall me?"
So that is thinking.
As we are talking now, people that have God seem to lose it again.
A lot of things are going on in your heart.
If you don't believe, you just think everything is money, money, money.
"How can somebody give me something like this? No!"
People lost God because they believe that they can't get anything -
"be healed!" - without money exchange.
You want God back? Give freely.
God is looking for people that will give freely.
Are you ready to give freely?
Even though you don't have, can you give freely?
Yes, give freely and see what will happen, your life will change suddenly.
Before you have abundant in your pocket - you don't have now - you can still give freely.
Soon you will have abundance.
We lost God because we believe we cannot give without receiving money.
Man of God, I want to beg for something.
Please, I need one fruit.
Not only you - you and your mummy should come and take a fruit.
No! If that will make her to follow Jesus fully, in fact I will ask her to carry the whole basket here.
As I will give you anything for the salvation of your soul.
She is not the one I delivered oo!
She now went to carry a fruit. Okay, carry it and go.
Okay, thank you!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
A better way to pay your tithes is to learn how to give out there free.
You know them - those who need what you have, give them freely.
You are paying your tithes.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Viewers all over the world, every good thing the Lord has given you,
use it to bless and care for those who are in need of what you have.
Those who are in need of what you have, you know them.
The poor, needy, widow, and those whom you are better - help them.
Like I have said, mere smile.
Just say to your neighbour, "I love you".
What a wonderful blessing.
And this must come from your heart.
When I say neighbour- it could be your enemy, those who do not share the same faith with you.
Say to them, "I love you" with all your heart.
Tell your neighbour.
I love you with all my heart.
Again.
Tell your neighbour again.
I love you with all my heart.
Again and again.
Love with all your heart.
It delivers one, it blesses one, it heals the wound of one.
We are not talking of fleshly love.
Say, "I love you with all my heart".
If I love you with all my heart, your wound will be healed.
You will feel the presence of God immediately.
Can you say to your neighbour, "I love you".
I love you.
I can't hear you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So can you rise up, and let me bless you with this language.
Rise up.
If you now go out and say "I love you" and it is not from your heart, you are raining curses on yourself.
It is a message, and you should live by this message.
Are you ready to receive the word 'love' in your heart?
Receive, in the name of Jesus!
When you love your neighbour with all your heart, you love God.
When you help your neighbour with all your heart, you help God.
When you greet your neighbour with all your heart, you greet God.
You have been helping people for so long.
God was not aware because this help was not from your heart.
You can give trillion dollars, billion pounds to people as a way of help,
but if it is not from your heart, you are wasting your time.
If your worship is not from your heart, you are wasting your time.
Christianity lies in the heart.
When you greet your neighbour with all your heart, you greet God.
When you help your neighbour with all your heart, you help God.
If you have being helping your neighbour with all your heart, God will help you, you will be helped.
Help; you will be helped.
Show mercy and you will receive mercy.
Show kindness and you will receive kindness.
You have been doing this, but not with all your heart.
This is why you keep asking yourself, "Look, I help people.
I do this. I trained this man, I helped this man, I paid the loan for this man.
I paid school fees for this man, I helped this man, I trained this man".
But at the end, it was opposite to you because all these were not from your heart.
You were doing them for the reason known to you.
Viewers, listen.
Just say to your neighbour - your neighbour could be your enemy,
those who do not share the same faith with you -
say to your neighbour, "I love you".
This must be with all your heart.
If you love your neighbour with all your heart, you love God.
If you love God, what happens, what comes next?
God will be your strength, your Provider.
If God becomes your Provider, what a blessing!
I command your heart to receive the word 'love'.
Love enough.
When you have this love we are talking about,
you will always see your contribution to others as God's responsibility.
Whatever you give, you give it to God.
Someone runs to you, someone is in need of help, you say, "Ah, this man is not a Christian".
And he is in need of help!
Can you see?
What are you reading in the Bible?
You need to move above your senses.
It is mere senses.
Tit for tat.
What is the message you are taking home now?
I love you.
Are you going to say that to your enemy?
Yes!
Those who do not share the same faith with you?
Yes.
Once again.
I love you.
Oh my God! Clap for Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TT: Ndinagwe Mwakigonja
RV: Mel Flowers 22/12/2018